Finding Aid for Michigan Legislature photograph collection, 1875-1990
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Michigan Legislature photograph collection 1875-1990
Michigan. Legislature.
3 oversize folders
93265 UCA.3m; UCA.3l
Group and composite portraits of the members of the Michigan Legislature.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was accumulated from different sources
No further additions to the papers are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Beginning around 1870, the Michigan Legislature produced group and composite portraits of its members.
This is a collection of group and composite portraits of the members of the Michigan Legislature. The photographs were accumulated from different sources.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Michigan. Legislature. House of Representatives.; Michigan. Legislature. Senate.; Politics and government.
Genre Terms:
Photographs.
- Group and composite portraits of the members of the Michigan Legislature
  - House of Representatives
    (in oversize folder UCA.3m unless otherwise indicated)
    - 1877/1878 (Folder UCA.3m)
    - 1883/1884 (Folder UCA.3m)
    - 1885/1886, copy print (Folder UCA.3m)
    - 1899/1900 (Folder UCA.3m)
    - 1903/1904 (Folder UCA.3l)
    - 1905/1906 (Folder UCA.3l)
    - 1919/1920 (Folder UCA.3m)
    - 1925/1926 (Folder UCA.3m)
    - 1989/1990 (Folder UCA.3m)
  - Senate
    - 1875/1876 (Folder UCA.3m)
    - 1877/1878 (Folder UCA.3m)
    - 1883/1884 group, composite, and "Kickers" (Folder UCA.3m)
    - 1921/1922 (Folder UCA.3m)
    - 1927/1928 (Folder UCA.3m)
    - 1929/1930 (Folder UCA.3m)